exsees.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy - NewsCentral

Privacy Policy

INTRODUCTION

Your privacy is essential to us. Here in NewsCentral.com (“NewsCentral” or “we” or “us”), we believe that privacy is a top priority. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared. Thus, we provide this Privacy Policy to summarize our procedures and practices as regards to information collection and use. This will serve you as a guide in making an intelligent decision in sharing your information with us. By visiting NewsCentral Website (the "Site" or the "Website"), you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and hereby accept the procedures and practices stated in this herein.

SCOPE

This Privacy Policy applies only within this website, all NewsCentral applications and services and other pages where this policy appears. This would describe and explain how we take care and handle your personal information you shared to us. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

COLLECTION & HOW USE

If you attempt to use the services and applications of our website and or choose to provide information to us, this website shall collect Personal Information from you. This information includes, but is not limited to: first name, last name and email address. In addition, NewsCentral collects usage information and any other information you transmit to us, in order to improve the service. Once collected, we will store your information for a reasonable period of time for record keeping purposes. The information that we store is sometimes deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business.

NewsCentral official applications (mobile application, extensions, add-ons, plug-ins and widgets) also may collect different kinds of information.

DISCLOSURE

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

COOKIES

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors.

USERS ACTIVITY AND PERSONAL INFORMATION

User activity and/or information may be publicly available on user profile page and/or any other pages/sources. This kind of information can be indexed by web crawlers and/or be taken by third parties without notice or permissions from NewsCentral.

SECURITY

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. We do everything in our power to protect Sensitive Information online and PII (including Sensitive Information) off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our end-users' personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

THIRD PARTIES

We provide content from and links to websites outside of our website, as well as to third party websites. In addition, we give you the possibility to add such content by yourself. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked from our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that website and its privacy statement.

NewsCentral may share users information but not PII with third parties.

While using NewsCentral website and its Services, for example in links sharing, some of your data may be exposed to third parties. These parties, with whom you choose to share your data, are not under our control, and this sharing is under your responsibility. Notice that these third parties may also share the data that you have shared with them, and we are not responsible for any of those outcomes.

CHANGES AND AMENDMENTS & NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

NewsCentral reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a clear and conspicuous notice on the Website explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check the Website periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Website and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.
